Panchkula, Haryana 9728671236

☑ ajaysuper11@gmail.com

Objective

Self-motivated team player with more than 2 years of experience seeking a position as a Angular/Front-End Web developer with Next Generation Web Development where I can apply my advanced knowledge of web development with my full abilities to meet client needs and exceed their expectations.

Work experience

Content Management System Executive - Intern

04/2019 - 07/2019

Trivone Digital Services

- Developed and edited content for websites for various events and news.
- Managed content management system and uploaded content on it on a regular basis.

Angular Developer

06/2020 - 05/2021

Liftgy.in

- WordPress based website for Latest news & bloggers.
- I'm working as Angular Developer Freelancer & integrating Angular with WordPress, through APIs.

Angular Developer

07/2021 - 11/2021

Dot Technologies

- A company with full IT solutions for their clients and customers
- I am working on a Dubai based client's project on Job Search and Post Website, as a Frontend/Angular Developer Freelancer.
- Coordinating with Website's backend Laravel REST APIs.

Technical Head 10/2021 - Present

GeeksForGeeks Student Chapters CUH

- GeeksForGeeks Student Chapters CUH Are Community Groups For College And University Students For Creating A Technical Environment Amongst Them.
- I am working as a Technical Head, my work is to create, maintain and update their website regularly.
- Tech Stacks used are Angular and Django and SQLite.

Front-End/Angular Developer

3/2022 - Present

The Tekkers

- Providers of Computer support and services.
- I am working as a Front End Developer Freelancer, on a School Website with PHP Backend and HTML CSS.
- My work is to update the website on regular basis
- Also working as an Angular Developer Freelancer, on Angular Projects.

Angular Developer

6/2022 - Present

ProCloudware Services Pvt. Ltd.

- IT Company with Computer and related Activities like maintenance of websites, etc.
- I am working as an Angular Developer Freelancer, on various Angular Projects.

Projects

Omizzy (A Job search & post website)

Worked on a live project with Angular front-end and Laravel back-end.

It is a job searching & posting website for a Dubai based client.

Using latest Angular versions 10+

Project URL:- https://omizzy.com/

Liftgy (A Full IT Solution Company)

Worked on a project with Angular front-end and Headless Wordpress back-end.

Using latest Angular versions 12+

Project URL:- https://liftgy.in/

GFG CUH (A Student Chapters website)

Worked on a live project with Angular front-end and Django back-end.

Using latest Angular versions 12+

Project URL:- https://gfg-studentchapters-cuh.github.io/gfgsc-cuh/home

Activities

Workshop on Machine Learning

Oct 2019

Actively attended Hands-on Workshop on Machine Learning using Python, organized by Sofcon India Pvt. Ltd. in association with the Central University of Haryana, and Skill India, Affiliated and Funded by National Skill Development Corporation (NSDC).

National Coding Competition

June 2020

Completed the Bronze Level in Teco Booster (C Programming) track of "Code Predator"- a three-track National Coding Competition with Teco Booster (C Programming), Pythogorean Inertia (Python), and Bytecode Pundits (Java) tracks.

Angular Course Completion

Sep 2020

Successfully completed 33.5 total hours of Angular - The Complete Guide (2020 Edition) online course on Udemy

Skills

Angular

TypeScript

JavaScript

HTML5/CSS3

VS Code

Education

B.Tech Computer Science & Engineering

Central University of Haryana 8.2 GPA till 6th Semester

2019 - Present

Intermediate (+2) in Non-Medical

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, Solan CBSE 90% score

2017 - 2018

Extra Curricular

- NCC 'A' certificate holder.
- Worked as a Vice-Captain of the School.
- Worked as a Class Captain.
- Regional Level Chess Player.
- Served as an NSS Cadet.
- Participated in Science Exhibition.
- 3rd Position holder in the Tech-Quiz (University Level).